All: Assalamu'alaikum warrahmatullahi wabarakatuh
Rudi: Hello guys, we're from E Team of Human Computer Interaction course! On the right-side corner is our Captain, Faris^^
Rudi: Tonight we're gonna discuss about a mobile app which we should be able to improve it.
Rudi: After a couple of days we used the mobile apps,
Rudi: So how's your respond, Faris?
(Oh by the way, the mobile apps we talked about is Tell.)
Faris: Well, IMO, it's my first time using this concept of a mobile app,
Faris: The concept is quite interesting
Faris: We can write stories as an anonymous and we didn't know about "who post what" because of the anonymous concept.
Faris: So, the concept is quite interesting. But, i think because Tell is still "new" so the UI needs to be improve
Rudi: How about you, Azzam?
Azzam: Tell has two features, Fun Corner and Stories. And in Stories, we can write as an anonym and posted it online,
Azzam: so i think it's a good feature where we can improve our writing skills. It's really a good idea.
Azzam: In Fun Corner, we can write anything we want without people knowing our identity.
Azzam: That's it.
Rudi: Okay, that's it from Azzam. It's my turn to give opinion, but for the record I used Tell only for few days,
Rudi: The good point about Tell is we can freely sharing (i.e. stories, confide etc) anything,
Rudi: And every people who used Tell will read it,
Rudi: Let's say there's person who shares their bad experience about something, then the other user who read it will be able to anticipated it.
Rudi: then the other user who read it will be able to anticipated it. That's my 1st opinion.
Rudi: My 2nd opinion, like Faris said,
Rudi: Tell is a place where we can share stories or messages without people knowing our identity.
Rudi: So we can freely tell everyone about anything including our bad or embarassing stories without fear.
Rudi: What can we improve about Tell?
Rudi: What is your opinion, Faris?
Faris: There's a lot. Wow, i sound so arrogant:(
Rudi: Spill it.
Faris: *laugh*
Faris: Because Tell is quite new, so the UI need to be improve because it's not visually appealing.
Faris: And some of interaction parts is less efficient.
Rudi: Can you be more spesific?
Rudi : *gibberish*
Rudi: Can you describe it in objective pov? Excluding the subjective pov (i.e. personal taste of color, etc etc)
Faris: On the dashboard page, there's menus for Fun Corner and Stories.
Faris: The illustration right above those menus is quite too big
Faris: So the user's first sight is the illustration, but IMO, those menus should be the user's first sight when they open the app.
Rudi: Do you mean that those menus should be the hightlight of the dashboard page?
Faris: Yes
Faris: And there's bug in the comment section of Stories,
Faris: When the comment section is empty, the notification that says "be the first one bla bla" is crushed into the comment box where we type our comment
Rudi & Faris: *clarifies*
Faris: That's it from me. Maybe Azzam wanna give his opinion about the app?
Rudi: Now your turn, Azzam.
Azzam: Here's the dashboard page.
Azzam: So this is the illustration that Faris talked about.
Azzam: Here's my opinion about what needs to be improve for Tell
Azzam: If we clicked the Stories menu button, it brings us to this page. The Profile menu located here,
Azzam: But, IMO, Profile page usually located either on Dashboard page or Settings page,
Azzam: So it's a bit weird for me to see Profile page on Stories. This needs to be improve.
Azzam: Another things that needs to be improved, if we look at the Stories page, there's Categories.
Azzam: And, there's Latest Stories right below the Categories.
Azzam: IMO, the Latest Stories should be placed inside the Categories. Let's take Love Life category as an example.
Azzam: Love Life should have two tabs-menu, such as Most Views and Latest Stories.
Azzam: Because, if the Latest Stories placed outside and right below the Categories, we didn't know what the genre of the story is.
Azzam: Let's take "Dear Mas" as an example. What if Dear Mas's genre turned out to be Horror?
(It's gonna be a big problem bcs, in user there must be one person who HATES horror.)
Azzam: So, we didn't know the genre of the Stories listed in the Lates Stories.
Rudi: Ah, so the unknown genre is gonna bring problem.
Azzam: Yes.
Azzam: And if we take a look at Fun Corner page,
Azzam: there's "Arts" as one of the categories. But, if we tapped Arts,
Azzam: The Users often posted about music and movies, so i think those two can be separated into new categories.
Azzam: So it's either added two new categories or replace Arts with Music and Movies categories.
Azzam: Ah, this is what Faris talked about, when the comment section is empty, the notification line crashed into the comment box.
Azzam: I think the cat bowl size should be reduced in order to lift up the notification line.
Azzam: So that's how to solved this problem.
Faris: But IMO, it's kinda useless to tell the user that the comment section is empty...
Rudi: I agree, it's better left the comment section blank to avoid the problem.
Faris: Yes that's true, no need to insert notification line.
Faris: Why the user need to know that the comment section is empy when they can see it with their own eyes?
Rudi: OR OR OR OR
Rudi: Or, remove the cat bowl pic so there's only the notification line on the empty comment section.
Azzam: Ah that's true, because here besides the bubble chat icon, there's an indicator number of how many people comment on this stories.
Azzam: Let's continue. So this is how it looks when we click into Education category in Fun Stories (I got mixed up between Fun Corner and Stories:( )
Azzam: Oops, I mean Fun Corner.
Azzam: So this is the timeline of Education category, as you can see that this is obviously anonymus.
Faris: FYI, it looks like this on every categories in Fun Corner.
Azzam: Yes that's true.
Azzam: For me, the UI is not too visually appealing.
Faris: Look at those bubble chat...
Azzam & Rudi: Yes, the bubble chat is quite unsightly.
Azzam: It just my subjective pov but I think it's not gonna make the user spend a long time here.
Rudi: Too basic, plain and standard
Azzam: So I think this page still can be improve.
Azzam: That's it from me.
Faris: I found another things that this app need to improve. Can I talk about it?
Azzam & Rudi: Spill it.
Faris: Do you guys see the orange-colored rounded thing right below theEducation tab?
Azzam: Ah yes, I saw it.
Faris: I think that's the notification bar, because it tells us about the upcoming iOS version of this app. IMO,
Faris: the notification bar should placed on the Dashboard page,
Rudi & Azzam: I think you're right.
Rudi: Because it easier for people to see it and it definitely gonna be seen by every user.
Azzam: Yes you're right
Azzam: Ah! I remember something, there's another thing that this app needs to be improve.
Azzam: I once posted at Fun Corner on Education categories, here you can look at my post that says "Fun main bla bla bla"
Faris: So it's true that you're the one who posted it?
Azzam: Yes, that's me
Faris: *laugh*
Azzam: The last time I checked, I found out that there's users who commented under my post. But, I didn't receive any notification
Azzam: So I didn't know that about the comments under my post.
Azzam: *talks gibberish*
Azzam: So I think this need to be improve
Rudi: Do you mean the "push to notification" feature?
Azzam: Well, yes, but what I mean is this notification icon.
Azzam: There's no sign that my post got commented on this notification icon
Azzam: So I think this needs to be improve too
Azzam: Because the notification icon should tell us when our post got likes or comments
Azzam: That's it from me.
Rudi: Well because my opinion is the same as my friends's, I don't have to repeat it again, right? *laugh*
Rudi: *gibberish*
Rudi: Is there anything you guys want to add? About things that needs to be improved from Tell?
Rudi: Anyone?
Faris: Hm...maybe Tell should add checkbox on their Dialogue Box that pop-up everytime we open the apps that asked us to grant permission to run in background.
Faris: Checkbox that says "Do not show this message again". Because, if you didn't give permission,
Faris:  the Dialogue Box keeps pop-up endlessly,
Faris: so it's kinda annoying
Rudi: Okay, Faris addition is Tell needs to add checkbox to avoid user getting annoyed
Faris & Rudi: *keep repeating the same thing again...*
Rudi: Okay, so we're gonna do this "challenge" (i.e. assignment)
Rudi: and we're gonna follow the Google Design Sprint method step-by-step,
Rudi: In the 1st day, we started by discussion about the mobile apps and recorded by Zoom Meeting Cloud,
Rudi: and on the 2nd day, we're gonna design our own UI based on "things need to be improve from the mobile app",
Rudi: and then we're gonna ask another Team to vote which design is the best among us,
Rudi: Is 2 days is enough for you guys to finish the design?
Rudi: Is it enough?
Azzam: Yes
Faris: Yes that's enough
Azzam: I'll try my best
Rudi: Well, the designers on our Team is Faris and Azzam, My role is just back up lol
Rudi: As for the 3rd days,
Rudi: I forgot to mention, the 1st day in our "Google Design Sprint calendar" is October 5th, 2020.
Rudi: And the designing process takes 2 days,
Rudi: on October 6th to October 7th, 2020.
Rudi: and then we're gonna hold a voting event to choose the best design among us
Rudi: on October 8th, 2020.
Rudi: On the next day, (October 9th, 2020),
Rudi: We're gonna presenting our improve design and discuss about it with the Tell developer team.
Rudi: *repeat the same line again*
Rudi: whether they acknowledge our own UI or not, it's not a big deal.
Faris: We only need their feedback
Azzam: I really wish we can do our schedule on October 9th
Rudi: I think that's enough for today's discussion.
Rudi: Is there anything you guys want to add?
Faris: *asking himself*
Azzam: I think that's enough for me. I don't want to add anything
Faris: No, because the rest of the app is pretty good, even they have feature to share the app to Discord.
Rudi: I agree, for a new app, Tell is quite good
Rudi: Alright then, let's continue to the voting days!